PATRICK LEE

Final Year MEng Computer Science Student Due to Graduate Summer 2024

Due to diadate Summer 2021

Self-directed and adaptable final year student with a solid background in Computer Science fundamentals, data structures and algorithms, with later specialism in more applied areas such as security, machine learning and computational neuroscience.

Currently looking for a software developer role, particularly at a startup where I can use my skills to really impact an exciting project.

patrick1ee.github.io/ patricklee927@gmail.com

\ +447711373630 \(\) github.com/patrick1ee

Paristol, UK in /in/patrick-lee-060491260

SKILLS

Languages:

C, Javascript/Typescript, Python, PostgreSQL, React Native, Vue JS, PHP, Symfony, C++, Go, Julia

Technologies: AWS, Docker, Git

PROJECTS -

SUMMARY

PHP, Typecript, PostgreSQL, AWS

QR/Landing Page Management Platform (Independent)

github.com/patrick1ee/keypin-web

Built both front and back end from the ground up, collborating with a designer using Figma. A company acting as a tester recorded over 700 interactions with their page which they had created using our platform, placing the generated QR codes on some of their product packaging.

Go, Typescript, React Native

Peer-to-peer futures betting app (Independent)

github.com/patrick1ee/slips

Implemented the front and back end of the platform using the Gin HTTP framework as well as writing unit and integration testing and ensuring database transactions adhere to ACID principles.

C, Python

AES Power Analysis Attacks & Countermeasures (Course)

github.com/patrick1ee/AttackHW

Developed AES encryption firmware for a micro-controller and created an efficient key recovery attack against it, revising to give a 10x speed increase on the initial version. Implemented successfull countermeasures for this attack, with consideration of device constraints. I also wrote a specification considering further threats and counter-measures for other functionality required for TLS communication.

Assembly, Python

ROP Shellcode Compiler For Antivirus Evasion (Course)

github.com/patrick1ee/CROPgadget

Group project in which we successfully built a tool that take certain Shellcodes and compile them into a ROPchain exploit, given binary vulnerable to buffer overflow, bypassing defences such as executable space protection, code signing and ASLR. We wrote a report evaluating our work and presenting research on possible countermeasures.

EDUCATION

9/2020 - present

MEng Computer Science (projected First Class Hons.)

University of Bristol

Specialising in Security, Machine Learning & Computational Neuroscience/Al

9/2012 - 8/2019

A-Level Maths, Computing, Physics & Further Maths at grades A*AAB

The Grange School

9 GCSEs at grades A*/9 and 1 at grade 7

EMPLOYMENT

7/2023 - present

Research Assistant & Software Engineer

University of Bristol

Python, Kotlin Typescript React Native Successfully added features to experimental neuroscience software and decreased overhead.

• Designed and implemented mobile app which, operated via a UI, uses audio-based hardware to provide stimulation as part of experimental treatment for Dystonia.

· Used patient feedback and data to improve the design and features of this app.

github.com/peafischer/EEGVIBE-dev github.com/peafischer/stop-dystonia-app

8/2021 - present Club/Events DJ Truth Tribe Ltd. 5/2022 - 8/2022 Front of House Brewhouse & Kitchen 4/2020 - 8/2020 Warehouse Picker 2/2020 - 4/2020 Security Morrisons Moe Joe's Nightclub 11/2019 - 4/2020 **Ski Instructor** 9/2019 - 11/2019 Factory Worker Vail Resorts Robert's Bakery 9/2019 - 11/2019 Maths Tutor 4/2017 - 9/2019 Lifeguard/Instructor Manley Mere Self-employed

HOBBIES/INTERESTS

I've always been a keen musician, playing both piano and saxophone to grades 5 and 7 respectively. In recent years I've worked as a DJ and event organiser as part of a collective started with friends from University, and this in turn has led to a recent interest in the development and modification of both music production software and hardware. This tied in well with my third year group project in which building a drum MIDI controller was a key aspect.

I also enjoy all things fitness related, from my captaincy of the rowing team during school and expeditions as part of the Duke of Edinburgh award to mountaineering and ski touring, developed from my time spent teaching skiing in Whistler.